She's the most maddening female he's ever met. And she's only six years old.
I'll Do Anything is a comedy, drama, music film directed by James L. Brooks.
Matt Hobbs is a talented but unsuccessful actor.
When estranged (and strange) ex-wife Beth dumps their daughter Jeannie on
Matt, father and daughter have a lot of adjusting to do.
His budding relationship with attractive production assistant Cathy Breslow is made
complicated, while the precocious child is overly accustomed to getting her own way.
Matt eventually faces the choice of family vs
career in a particularly difficult way.
Matt Hobbs, played by Nick Nolte.
Jeannie Hobbs, played by Whittni Wright.
Burke Adler, played by Albert Brooks.
Nan Mulhanney, played by Julie Kavner.
Cathy Breslow, played by Joely Richardson.
Beth Hobbs, played by Tracey Ullman.
I'll Do Anything is a 1994 American comedy-drama
film written and directed by James L.
While a large part of the film is a satire of the film industry,
it also skewers relationships from various angles.
Its primary plot concerns a down-on-his-luck actor who suddenly finds
himself the sole caretaker of his six-year-old daughter.
The film starred Nick Nolte and Whittni Wright in her film debut, with supporting roles
filled by Albert Brooks, Julie Kavner, Joely Richardson and Tracey Ullman.
I'll Do Anything was released by Columbia Pictures on February 4, 1994.
The film received mixed to positive reviews from critics but was a box office
bomb as it grossed $10 million against a $40 million budget.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.